<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Practical Data]]></title>
  <link href="http://practicaldata.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://practicaldata.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2013-07-29T11:37:53-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://practicaldata.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Werner and DeGangi]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[werner_intro]]></title>
    <link href="http://practicaldata.github.io/blog/blog/2013/07/29/werner-intro/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-29T11:33:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://practicaldata.github.io/blog/blog/2013/07/29/werner-intro</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So I&rsquo;m Drew, and I&rsquo;m half of the practicaldata blogging pair.  A bit about me: I&rsquo;m a math and physics guy who most recently spent time at a quantitative hedge fund working on various and sundry analytics tasks.  Before that, I spent about a cool half decade as a patent lawyer.</p>

<p>Enough of the pleasantries.  I started this blog with Tony as a way to write about our shared interests in the many and varied applications of predictive analytics to real-world data, as well as provide an accessible and (hopefully) entertaining way to describe our approach to the various challenges that arise in creating real-world, data-drieven application.  We&rsquo;ve also been told that wealth and power beyond our wildest dreams is a natural result of starting a data blog, and so we look forward to that happening over the coming weeks.</p>

<p>In the coming posts, and with the help of some motivating examples, I plan to focus on:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Basic ideas in predictive analytics</li>
  <li>Experimenting with data</li>
  <li>Building robust models</li>
</ul>


<p>Tony will also be contributing with a focus on deployment issues, frontend visualizations, and probably some other stuff he&rsquo;s keeping from me.</p>

<p>Anyhow, stay tuned here for more excitement along the above lines.  Thanks for reading.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
